



14.08.1993



jonitirkkonenmusic@gmail.com



Tilankuja 8 B 37 01800 Klaukkala



+358 50 559 4488



<u> LinkedIn</u>



<u>GitHub</u>

SKILLS

IT

- Javascript
- HTML5
- CSS
- Java
- MS Office 365
- CCNA 1
- Active Directory
- GIMP
- Audacity
- SAP
- Microsoft Dynamics NAV
- · Social Media

Language

- Finnish Native
- English Professional
- Swedish Fundamentals
- German Fundamentals

JONI TIRKKONEN

PROFILE

BBA student in the field of ICT at Haaga-Helia university of applied sciences.

The goal is to become as a software developer and for that willing to gain strong technical knowledge and to learn more about different business information systems.

Extroverted person with experience in international working environments.

WORK EXPERIENCE

09/2007 - (present)

Klaukkalan Rakennustyö

Oy

IT Officer

(Previous title: Logistics

manager).

05/2020 - 11/2020

Palvelukeskus Helsinki

ICT Support Officer (Technical customer support

for ICT solutions provided by the city of Helsinki).

08/2018 - 06/2019

Neste K Kannelmäki

Gas Station Cashier

05/2017 - 11/2017

SYKES Enterprises Berlin

Technical Customer Support,

Sony

EDUCATION

08/2021 - (12/2024)

08/2018 - 12/2020

Haaga-Helia UAS, Helsinki

ICT, Bachelor of Business

Administration

Metropolia UAS, Espoo

ICT, engineering